{
  "LevelId": 19,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 188,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BLACKBUCK",
      "question": "Indian antelope species with distinctive spiral horns"
    },
    {
      "id": 189,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "DIZZINESS",
      "question": "Sensation of lightheadedness or unsteadiness"
    },
    {
      "id": 190,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BRILLIANT",
      "question": "Exceptionally intelligent or bright"
    },
    {
      "id": 191,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "APOLOGIZE",
      "question": "Express regret or remorse for a wrongdoing"
    },
    {
      "id": 192,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "AUTOMATIC",
      "question": "Operating independently without human intervention"
    },
    {
      "id": 193,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "BUTTERFLY",
      "question": "Insect with colorful wings and a transformative life cycle"
    },
    {
      "id": 194,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "AUDITIONS",
      "question": "Tryouts or interviews for a role in a performance or competition"
    },
    {
      "id": 195,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "ORCHESTRA",
      "question": "Large ensemble of musicians playing various instruments"
    },
    {
      "id": 196,
      "level_image": 5,
      "answer_text": "UNDERTONE",
      "question": "Subtle or underlying quality or feeling"
    },
    {
      "id": 197,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "KILOMETER",
      "question": "Unit of measurement for distance, equal to 1,000 meters"
    }
  ]
}